### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/mrsid0211 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Modbus communication Teamwork

**Team Motivation** 

## Languages

English (Professional Working) Hindi (Professional Working)

### Certifications

NoSQL database

Analyzing and Visualizing Data with Microsoft Power BI

Introduction to Programming Using Python

**Pandas** 

SQL

# Sudheer Vishwakarma

Electrical engineer

New Delhi, Delhi, India

# Summary

Working as Commissioning engineer at Endress & Hauser India Pvt Ltd.

Our client is Uttar Pradesh Jal Nigam. My responsibility are overseeing installation, commissioning and pre-commissioning as well as conducting tests and inspections to ensure operational effectiveness of utilities. Planning of Projects, Maintenance and Commissioning. Good Co-ordination & interaction with higher authorities, client & sub-contractor and work related other department.

Experience on field instruments like Level, Flow, Spectrometer, ISE, pH sensors etc.

Experience on Install, upgrade, support, and troubleshoot Windows OS, authorized desktop applications, hardware, and peripheral equipment.

# Experience

SUNTECH ENGI-AUTOMATION PRIVATE LIMITED

Commissioning Engineer
July 2022 - Present (1 year 2 months)

Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh, India

#### JMS ENTERPRISES LLC

Desktop Support Engineer trainee December 2020 - January 2022 (1 year 2 months) Uttar Pradesh, India

Diesel Locomotive Works
Summer Internship
July 2017 - July 2017 (1 month)
Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh, India

Education

# BABU BANARASI DAS NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY AND MANAGEMENT, LUCKNOW

BTech - Bachelor of Technology, Electrical Engineering · (2014 - 2018)